Guide to the George Langdon, Associate Provost, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
George Langdon, associate provost, Yale University, records
1965-1979
RU 788
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
11.25
(9 boxes)
The records consist of subject files maintained by George Langdon as associate provost of Yale University.
Yale University. Office of the Provost
Langdon, George D.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 3-B (YRG 3-B), Records of Yale deputy, associate, and assistant provosts.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the Office of the Provost, 1992.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of subject files maintained by George Langdon as associate provost of Yale.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Universities and colleges -- Administration; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University. Office of the Provost
- Records of George Langdon as associate provost, 1968-1978; Accession 1992-A-056
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2013.
  - University Parking, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - University Parking, 1973-1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - School of Organization and Management, 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Yale Parking Service, 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 4-6)
  - Provosts contingency fund, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Provosts weekly meeting (Monday), 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Psychology, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Pro Musica, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Personnel, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Naval Science (correspondence), 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Outdoor recreation center, 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Political Science (correspondence), 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Urban Studies, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Work study program, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Yale reports, 1970-1974 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - YNFAC, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Yale Film Associates, 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Yale Educational TV, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Tuition postponement, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - University Operations, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 22-24)
  - Upward Bound, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Unemployment compensation forms, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Contingency repayment loan, 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Exceptions to the freeze, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Sociology (correspondence), 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Space, 1967-1970 (Box 2, Folder 30-32)
  - Summer programs, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 33-35)
  - Law School, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Library, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Map Lab, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - MAT, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - School of Medicine, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 40-42)
  - Medieval Studies, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Microbiology, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Military Science, 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Mellon Center, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - School of Music (correspondence), 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Mortgage loans, 1969-1971 (Box 2)
  - Office of the Provost, 1967-1972 (Box 2)
  - Office of the Treasurer, 1971-1973 (Box 2)
  - Office of the President, 1970-1973 (Box 2)
  - Patent Committee, 1971-1978 (Box 3)
  - Postdoctoral research appointments-policies and procedures, 1973 (Box 3)
  - Postdoctoral Fellows Committee, 1970-1976 (Box 3)
  - Research Appointments Structure, 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Research Appointments Structure, 1973 (Box 3)
  - Research Appointments Structure, 1973-1976 (Box 3)
  - University Radiation Safety Committee, 1971-1978 (Box 3)
  - Reproductive Biology, 1971-1973 (Box 3)
  - Space problems, 1975-1977 (Box 3)
  - Space alloaction, 1973-1978 (Box 3)
  - Shops, 1975-1977 (Box 3)
  - Electroncis design lab, 1975-1978 (Box 3)
  - Stockrooms, 1974-1977 (Box 3)
  - Stockrooms, 1975-1978 (Box 3)
  - Summer Studies Program, 1973-1974 (Box 3)
  - Physical Sciences Facility Advisory Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Thesis proposals evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 3)
  - Upward Bound, 1973-1977 (Box 3)
  - Yale College, 1975-1976 (Box 3)
  - University Operations, 1973-1977 (Box 3)
  - Educational policy meeting, 1973-1976 (Box 4)
  - Education of Women Committee, 1973 (Box 4)
  - Employment, 1968-1973 (Box 4)
  - Energy conservation, 1973 (Box 4)
  - Committee on Employment Policy in Colleges, 1971-1973 (Box 4)
  - Faculty benefit information, 1968-1973 (Box 4)
  - faculty panorams, 1968-1972 (Box 4)
  - faculty appointments, 1968-1970 (Box 4)
  - Fareastern publications, 1969-1973 (Box 4)
  - Financial aid, 1969-1973 (Box 4)
  - Foundations, 1968-1970 (Box 4)
  - Financial aid (Yale College), 1967-1970 (Box 4)
  - Judaica series, 1968-1972 (Box 4)
  - Funds, 1969-1973 (Box 4)
  - Funds (Development), 1970 (Box 4)
  - Funds (Provost's endowment), 1973-1975 (Box 4)
  - Grants and Contracts, 1968-1971 (Box 4)
  - Grants and Contracts, 1971-1972 (Box 4)
  - Grants and Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 4)
  - Housing, 1970-1973 (Box 4)
  - Housing (cont'd), 1971-1973 (Box 5)
  - Co-education housing, 1968-1970 (Box 5)
  - Co-education, 1970-1973 (Box 5)
  - Undergraduate housing, 1968-1970 (Box 5)
  - New housing, 1970 (Box 5)
  - Housing Executive Committee, 1970 (Box 5)
  - International Office, 1970-1972 (Box 5)
  - Concilim on International Studies, 1970-1973 (Box 5)
  - Inquiries re: policy, 1971-1973 (Box 5)
  - Institutional Research, 1971-1973 (Box 5)
  - Leaves of absence, 1969-1973 (Box 5)
  - Mortgage loans, 1971-1973 (Box 5)
  - New colleges, 1971-1973 (Box 5)
  - Norfolk, 1972-1973 (Box 5)
  - Italian Department, 1971-1973 (Box 6)
  - Spanish and Italian, 1970-1972 (Box 6)
  - Language Committee, 1970-1973 (Box 6)
  - Law School, 1970-1973 (Box 6)
  - Library, 1971-1973 (Box 6)
  - Linguistics, 1968-1973 (Box 6)
  - Mathematics, 1968-1973 (Box 6)
  - School of Medicine, 1971-1976 (Box 6)
  - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry, 1969-1973 (Box 6)
  - Music Department, 1968-1973 (Box 6)
  - Music School, 1971-1973 (Box 6)
  - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures, 1968-1973 (Box 6)
  - School of Nursing, 1966-1973 (Box 6)
  - Physics, 1969-1972 (Box 6)
  - Philosophy, 1968-1973 (Box 6)
  - Political Science, 1971-1973 (Box 6)
  - Psychiatry, 1969-1972 (Box 6)
  - Psychology Department, 1970-1973 (Box 6)
  - Religious Studies, 1969-1973 (Box 6)
  - Romance Languages, 1968-1973 (Box 6)
  - Slavic Languages and Literatures, 1968-1973 (Box 6)
  - Sociology, 1970-1973 (Box 6)
  - Spanish, 1970-1973 (Box 6)
  - Statistics, 1970-1973 (Box 6)
  - Accoutns-budgeting (working committee), 1969-1970 (Box 6)
  - Administrative sciences correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 6)
  - Affirmative Action, 1970-1973 (Box 6)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1971-1973 (Box 7)
  - APTR meetings and agendas, 1969-1973 (Box 7)
  - Associated student agencies, 1972-1978 (Box 7)
  - Audio Visual Center, 1973 (Box 7)
  - Auditing, 1971-1973 (Box 7)
  - Black workshop, 1970-1971 (Box 7)
  - Buildings and Grounds Advisory Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 7)
  - Campus Security, 1969-1973 (Box 7)
  - Deputy Provost of the Sciences, 1969-1973 (Box 7)
  - Co-Education (committee, agenda, documents), 1969-1970 (Box 7)
  - Comptroller, 1969-1972 (Box 7)
  - Council of Masters, 1969-1973 (Box 7)
  - Council on Community Affairs, 1970-1971 (Box 7)
  - Economic growth, 1968-1973 (Box 7)
  - Afro-American Studies, 1970-1973 (Box 7)
  - Anthropology, 1969-1973 (Box 7)
  - Art Gallery, 1969-1973 (Box 7)
  - Art, 1971-1972 (Box 7)
  - Art and Architecture, 1969-1971 (Box 7)
  - Athletics, 1970-1973 (Box 8)
  - Biology, 1973 (Box 8)
  - Center for British Art and British Studies, 1967-1973 (Box 8)
  - Chemistry, 1973 (Box 8)
  - Classics Department, 1968-1973 (Box 8)
  - Computer Center, 1970-1971 (Box 8)
  - Computer Science, 1970-1973 (Box 8)
  - Comparative Literature, 1968-1972 (Box 8)
  - Culinary Institute, 1970-1974 (Box 8)
  - Divinity School, 1968-1973 (Box 8)
  - Bekeley Divinity School, 1971-1973 (Box 8)
  - Drama School, 1968-1973 (Box 8)
  - East Asian languages and Literatures, 1968-1973 (Box 8)
  - East Asian Studies, 1972-1974 (Box 8)
  - Economics Correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 8)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, 1970-1973 (Box 8)
  - English, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
  - Far Eastern Languages, 1970-1972 (Box 8)
  - School of Forestry, 1968-1973 (Box 8)
  - French, 1972-1973 (Box 8)
  - Geology and Geophysics, 1969-1973 (Box 9)
  - German, 1968-1973 (Box 9)
  - Graduate School, 1971-1973 (Box 9)
  - History correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 9)
  - History of Art, 1968-1973 (Box 9)
  - History of Sciecne and Medicine, 1973 (Box 9)
  - National Humanities Institute, 1973 (Box 9)
  - Institute for Sacred Music, 1973 (Box 9)
  - Institute for Social and Policy Studies, 1969-1973 (Box 9)